>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 在这次的提升过程中，你会有机会
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: In this hoisting
exercise, you're gonna get a chance to
将函数从其作用域中移出的做法 ( 如果它们 )
practice with that idea of bringing
functions out of their scopes if they
不需要嵌套或使用作用域底部的函数。
don't need to be nested, or
using functions at the bottom of scopes.
就像我们在演讲中提到的那样
That sort of thing like we've
just talked about in the lecture,
你会有机会练习的
you're gonna get a chance
to practice with that.
所以我们要用一个已经使用了各种功能的现有代码库
So we're gonna take an existing code base
that already uses a variety of function
表达式，我们将使用我们的新发现重构该代码库
expressions, and we're going to refactor
that code base using our newfound
关于提升的知识，我们改变它所写的方式的能力。
knowledge of hoisting, our ability
to change the way that it's written.
我们没有改变任何行为，只是简单地改变编码方式。
We're not changing any behavior, we're
just simply changing the coding style.
如果你看它的当前版本，它看起来就像这样。
If you look at the current version of it,
It looks like this.
我们有一组函数声明和内联函数表达式
We have a set of function declarations and
inline function expressions,
还有几个地方有内联函数表达式
and there are several places where
we have inline function expressions
不需要直接插入函数表达式。
that don't really need to be
inline function expressions.
举个例子，就在这里。
Once such example, right here.
该函数表达式本身不使用任何词法变量，因此
That function expression isn't using any
of the lexical variables around itself, so
没有什么特别的理由去直接插入它除了一种风格的偏好
there's no particular reason to inline it,
other than maybe just a style preference.
但没有机械的理由这样做。
But there's no mechanical reason to do so.
所以用我们知道的函数声明和
So using what we know about
function declarations and
功能提升让我们把它拉出来
function hoisting,
let's pull that one out.
所以你找
So you look for
可以将函数拉出外部作用域的示例，
those examples where functions can
be pulled out to an outer scope,
如果不需要嵌套，则使范围更简单，更平坦。
if they don't need to be nested, that
makes simpler and flatter scope structure.
而你所拥有的范围结构越简单
And the simpler and
flatter the scope structure you have,
越容易阅读和理解
the easier it will be to read and
understand.
越嵌套越越越越越越越越越越越越越越接近
The more nested it is, the harder it is
to keep track of all those boundaries.
另外，您将注意到所有可执行代码位于底部
Also, you'll notice that all
the executable code is at the bottom
这个项目的。
of this program.
我们学到的功能提升是我们可以将可执行的
And what we learned about function
hoisting is that we can put executable
顶部的代码，以及底部的所有功能。
code at the top, and
all the functions at the bottom.
所以你的任务是去重新考虑或者重新安排这些功能，
So your task is to sort of refactor,
or rearrange, these functions,
在必要时把它们拉出来
pull them out where necessary,
And refactor this code so
使用或利用功能提升的好处。
that it uses or leverages
the benefits of function hoisting.